<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">GamifyHealth</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_select_activities">SelectActivities</string>
    <string name="intro_string">Welcome to Gamify Your Health. This application is designed to </string>
    <string name="title_activity_current_activity_level">CurrentActivityLevel</string>
    <string name="preference_file_key">com.cs400.gamifyhealth.PREFERENCE_FILE_KEY</string>
    <string name="activity_types_REP">Crunches,Pull-Ups,Push-Ups,Squats,Dips</string>
    <string name="activity_types_DTA">Running (Time),Running (Distance),Swimming (Time),Swimming (Distance),Cycling (Time),Cycling (Distance)</string>
    <string name="title_activity_goal_set">GoalSetActivity</string>
    <string name="safe_mode_description">Safe Mode is intended for users who cannot work out due to injury or illness. When Safe Mode is enabled, monster attacks do not occur.</string>
    <string name="reset_description">Clears all workout data, goals, and activity preferences. Returns gameplay elements to a fresh install state.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_navigation_drawer_main">NavigationDrawerMain</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Drawer Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Drawer Closed</string>
    <string name="population">population</string>
    <string name="finalgoalstring">Final Goal: </string>
    <string name="weeklygoalstring">Weekly Goal: </string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="edit_activity_string">Add or remove activities from your current set.</string>
    <string name="data_entry_string">Enter today\'s workout information.</string>
    <string name="goal_entry_string">Enter how much on average you currently do this activity per week. </string>
    <string name="goal_entry_string2">Enter how much you want to do this activity per week, and in how many weeks you want to reach this level. </string>
    <string name="people1">A member of your village has contracted and spread itching disease!</string>
    <string name="people2">Boils. Everyone has boils.</string>
    <string name="people3">A traveling prophet has foretold that the end is nigh. Some of the villagers flee.</string>
    <string name="people4">Your village\'s water supply has been polluted.</string>
    <string name="people5">An epidemic of the bubonic plague has spread to your village.</string>
    <string name="farm1">A mild drought has caused crops to perform poorly this month.</string>
    <string name="farm2">A blight of locusts has invaded your village and eaten through your crops!</string>
    <string name="farm3">A powerful storm has washed away valuable farmland and equipment.</string>
    <string name="farm4">The master thief Yuen Hsi has snuck into your village and stolen some food.</string>
    <string name="farm5">A family of dragons has burned through your crops.</string>
    <string name="fort1">A freakishly large and ferocious bear has rampaged through the village.</string>
    <string name="fort2">Bandits have raided your village and stolen valuable weapons.</string>
    <string name="fort3">A tribe of barbarians has attacked your village.</string>
    <string name="fort4">Your people favor Pacifism. They have dismantled some fortifications.</string>
    <string name="fort5">A neighboring kingdom has attacked your village.</string>
    <string name="houses1">Heavy rain has caused massive flooding throughout the village.</string>
    <string name="houses2">A lightning strike to a thatched roof has caused a fire to break out.</string>
    <string name="houses3">The housing bubble has burst. Families now face foreclosure and demolition of their homes.</string>
    <string name="houses4">Your village has a growing termite infestation.</string>
    <string name="houses5">A pack of giants has trampled through your village.</string>
    <string name="houseDescription1">A virtually rodent-free enclosure. The perfect starter home for your village\'s families.</string>
    <string name="houseDescription2">Are your villagers sick of sleeping on the floor in their huts? Try this compact, cozy dwelling featuring multiple rooms and mattresses.</string>
    <string name="houseDescription3">Have you always dreamed of having horses and sheep right outside your window? This house is not equipped for stabling animals, but it\'s got plenty of rustic charm! And windows!</string>
    <string name="houseDescription5">A country estate worthy of the finest nobles.</string>
    <string name="houseDescription4">Now that\'s a big house. I bet you could fit a dragon in here. But maybe don\'t try that; not exactly fire-proof.</string>
    <string name="farmDescription1">A whole field of wheat. Perfect for making bread. Peasants love bread.</string>
    <string name="farmDescription2">A diverse patch of vegetables sure to keep your people healthy.</string>
    <string name="farmDescription3">A place to keep your cows and sheep and horses. For milking? Shearing? Eating? You decide.</string>
    <string name="farmDescription4">Mmm. Corn. Your villagers will eat this up.</string>
    <string name="farmDescription5">What a beautiful way to spend the day - strolling through the apple trees with sun on your face... The villagers are going to love this place.</string>
    <string name="fortDescription1">A basic siege weapon. Probably better for attacking than defending, but your villagers will take what they can get.</string>
    <string name="fortDescription2">This may look like a pile of rubble, and it certainly is. But those heavy, jagged stones are more than a match for most human foes.</string>
    <string name="fortDescription3">The tallest guard tower around! You\'ll see the enemy coming from miles away. Doubles as a panic room for the village.</string>
    <string name="fortDescription4">Walls of weapons. Enough said.</string>
    <string name="fortDescription5">More extensive walls of weapons. Plus solid rock walls lined with steel for good measure. Plus a library of military history!</string>


</resources>